[
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is a built-in React hook?",
        "answers":[
            "useState",
            "useFetch",
            "useLocalStorage",
            "useTimeout"],
        "correctAnswer":0
    },
    {
        "question":"What is the correct order of these lifecycle phases?",
        "answers":[
            "unmount, update, mount",
            "mount, update, unmount",
            "update, mount, unmount",
            "mount, unmount, update"],
        "correctAnswer":1
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following command is used to create react-js-app ?",
        "answers":[
            "npx create-react-app appname",
            "npm install create-react-app",
            "npx install create-react-app -g",
            "install - l create-react-app"],
        "correctAnswer":0
    },
    {
        "question":"In React.js which one of the following is used to create a class for Inheritance ?",
        "answers":[
            "Create",
            "Extends",
            "Inherits",
            "Delete"
        ],
        "correctAnswer":1
    },
    {
        "question":"What is the default port number in which the application run ?",
        "answers":[
            "3000",
            "5500",
            "8080",
            "3030"
        ],
        "correctAnswer":0
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is a way to handle data in React.js ?",
        "answers":[
            "State & Props",
            "Services & Components",
            "State & Services",
            "State & Component"
        ],
        "correctAnswer":0
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is true regarding Babel ?",
        "answers":[
            "Compiler",
            "Transpilar",
            "Both of the above",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correctAnswer":2
    },
    {
        "question":"In React.js, how we can pass the data from one component to another in React.js ?",
        "answers":[
            "SetState",
            "Render with arguments",
            "Props",
            "PropTypes"
        ],
        "correctAnswer":2
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is true about key props ?",
        "answers":[
            "Key props are used to look beauty",
            "Key prop is a way to identify the newly added element",
            "It is one type of attribute of HTML",
            "It is not used in the array"
        ],
        "correctAnswer":1
    },
    {
        "question":"What is the best definition of React.js ?",
        "answers":[
            "Server-side Framework",
            "User-interface framework",
            "A Library for building interactive interfaces",
            "None of These"
        ],
        "correctAnswer":2
    }
]